[{"answer": "Well, I mean I think the sources behind this are incredibly courageous people who could have sold this information for extraordinary amounts of money to foreign governments or handed it over, had that been their objective to harm the United States to enemies of the United States.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Are you worried now that they're going to come after you, big brother style, and try and come after your sources?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, it's fascinating that the most right-wing members of the Congress like Mike Rogers and Lindsey Graham have become the administration's most vocal defenders.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "But I mean, what is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, under the Surveillance Law that passed in 2008, that the bipartisan Congress passed, they eliminated the warrant requirement for all conversations except ones that take place by and among Americans exclusively on American soil.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Was their primary purpose to root out Americans who may be up to no good or foreigners who are up to no good?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I -- there may be some technical basis on which they can say that we are not actively collaborating or that they don't have what we consider in our own definition to be direct access to our servers but what I do know is that I have talked to more than one person who has sat at a desk at a Web portal and typed out commands and reached into those servers from a distance.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "You believe them?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, it depends entirely how they're using it and that's the problem with the secrecy here.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Senator, this is just unbelievable, isn't it?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Not to my mind it's not.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "That's not freedom, is it?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I think Bush started the process and what I had hoped and I think millions of Americans had hoped, that Barack Obama, who knew something about constitutional law, would not only change Bush's policies in a number of ways, but certainly with regard to civil liberties.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Has what Barack Obama has been doing, and his administration, not just with all these revelations in the last 24 hours but also the IRS and going after A.P. and FOX News and so on, when you put it all together, is what he's doing worse than anything George W. Bush did?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, we know they're not.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "How do we know they're not?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Do we?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "And we still don't know --", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Didn't you know that they were targeting Tea Party members through the IRS?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, I think, Piers, one of the big problems here has been that our society, the American people, and the Congress, and the media, have basically said to the authorities, to the FBI, to the CIA, and other intelligence services, we will not tolerate one single terrorist death, and that's the problem we've had, is that we had the terrible events of 9/11 and 12 years later, you know, if one or two or four or five people get killed in a terrorist attack, people are outraged, the FBI dropped the ball, why didn't they know about this, how come they can't read the bad guys' minds.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "But at what point do you draw the line, do you think?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, that's absolutely true, that you would not have had this capability.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "So it's kind of a symptom, really, of modern times, isn't it?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I actually -- I did know that he was going to do it.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Did you know your son was going to do this?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, I would have absolutely been as supportive.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Would the audience have been as supportive?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I don't think he would -- something like that would have had that kind of a reaction.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "But how do you think it would have played out?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "I think it's incredibly important.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "How important is it for people like your son maybe to stand up on behalf of the young and say what he did?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, I think Mr. Dershowitz got it right.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "You agree?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "That's the question.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Where do you draw the line?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know exactly what they've done here.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "ORGAN: Where would you draw the line?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Look, the city of New York, I don't believe, has that power or will ever have that power.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "I live in New York, if you become mayor, are you going to start snooping on my e-mails?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Would you like it to?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "You know, look --", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "I mean, you're still ahead of him but he's creeping up, isn't he?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Look, that's for New Yorkers to decide.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Is it appropriate for New Yorkers to vote as their mayor somebody who sent naked pictures of himself over the Internet to random women?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I know New Yorkers are going to vote for the candidate, me, who has the longest record of delivering for them because what they care about is that -- they've gotten and are going to get more housing.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What do you think as a New Yorker?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's very tough when you lose a parent when you're young and she was sick for about 10 years so most of my time with her, she was sick and it's hard because you feel as a child that somehow you're responsible, even though you know you're not.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "How did you come through it?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "You look fantastic to me.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "I don't -- I mean, everybody in the world has issues with food, right?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not bulimic now.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Do you ever recover fully from bulimia?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Look, the case --", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "You support -- what's happened here?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Under Texas law, this is perfectly legal.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "And a jury -- and a jury acquitted the guy.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "You support it?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I can't say --", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "You shoot a woman dead because she may or may not have taken $150?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Look, I can't say I agree with the Texas law, either.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "And a jury, and a courtroom in America, allows you to just walk out and go home to do it again?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "No, I don't agree with the Texas law.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Do you not?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130606pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "This story I had earlier about this high school valedictorian speech, are you in favor of it, Margaret?", "qSentId": 595}]